[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JUNE] Look at this idiot.
He's thinking about basketball
instead of apologizing.
Tch. He's so annoying.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[YOUNG TOTO]
You're amazing, Ping!
[YOUNG PING] It's because
my teammate's the best!
You look so handsome
when you smile.
If only you would
look at me like that.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[TOTO ON THE PHONE]
Hello, Ping?
I know you're looking for me.
I also know that your company
is filing an estafa case
against me.
But I only did it because
the people I owed money to
were pressuring me.
So, please, Ping,
withdraw the case against me.
I don't even know
where I'm safe anymore.
Please, Ping.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[PING] Why don't you ever learn?
No matter what I do, you just
keep doing it again and again.
[PHONE RINGING]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
[PHONE BEEPS]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TWIG CREAKS]
Who's there?
- [MOUSE SQUEAKING]
- [SCREAMING] Aah!
It's a rat! Aah!
Aah! It's a rat! Aah!
[PING]
What are you even doing here?
[SCREAMING] Aah!
Ow!
Enough! I'm safe now!
You're hurting me!
- What were you doing here?
- That really hurt!
You're spying on me, aren't you?
[SILLY MUSIC PLAYING]
Was that your brother?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]